We are all…
Hostiles is a drama, western, history film directed by Scott Cooper.
A legendary Native American-hating Army captain nearing retirement in 1892 is given one last assignment: to
escort a Cheyenne chief and his family through dangerous territory back to his Montana reservation.
Captain Joseph J. Blocker, played by Christian Bale.
Rosalee Quaid, played by Rosamund Pike.
Chief Yellow Hawk, played by Wes Studi.
Lieutenant Rudy Kidder, played by Jesse Plemons.
Black Hawk, played by Adam Beach.
Master Sergeant Thomas Metz, played by Rory Cochrane.
Hostiles is a 2017 American Western drama film written and
directed by Scott Cooper, based on a story by Donald E.
It stars Christian Bale, Rosamund Pike, Wes Studi, and Ben Foster; Stephen Lang, Jesse Plemons, Rory Cochrane,
Adam Beach, Q'orianka Kilcher, Jonathan Majors, and Timothée Chalamet appear in supporting roles.
It follows a U.S.
Army cavalry officer in 1892 who must escort a Cheyenne war
chief and his family back to their home in Montana.
The film had its world premiere on September 2,
2017, at the Telluride Film Festival.
It had a limited release in the United States by Entertainment Studios
beginning December 22, 2017, before going wide on January 26, 2018.
It received generally positive reviews from critics,
and grossed $35.7 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of widow, montana, new mexico, chief, native american.
The tone is dark and emotional.